Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial, 154271
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, 154278; (35 audiocassettes)
        - Amirkhanian, Charles. New Works 1981-1982, 1983 May 30; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:43:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503736)
          A handwritten liner note reads: Souvenir of San Francisco for Henri Chopin with best wishes! Charles Mirkhanian.
          1. "Dog of Stravinsky"
          2. "Hypothetical Moments"
          3. "Maroa"
          4. "History of Collage"
          5. "Church Car II"
          1. "The Putts"
          2. "Pastor"
          3. "Andas"
          4. "Dot Bunch"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&16c2572e-a2d2-4433-a6fd-b8ec44df534c
        - Chopin, Henri and Vonna-Michell, Erik. To Ray the Rays, 1985 August 21; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:09:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503744)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4d0a5264-18c4-4627-bf6c-317e1dd4cda1
        - Minarelli, Enzo. Untitled, 1984 August 30; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:26:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503751)
          A handwritten message on the audiocassette's liner notes reads: For Henri Chopin, Enzo Minarelli, 1984-08-30. The contents of the audiocassette are listed below.
          Kandinsky; 3'10", 1979
          Chorus; 4'10", 1983
          Rapsodissea; 12'55", 1983
          Wow Flutter Stop; 6'45", 1983
          Res Tauro; a. fermatura; 5'20", b. protezione; 6'20", c. foderatura; 7'20", 1983
          Fisch ìo; 3'53", 1984
          Echair; 2'40", 1984
          Urloh!; 3'45", 1984
          Anacoluto; 2'50", 1984
          Rebut-Rebus; 3'25", 1984
          Accenti; 2'00", 1984
          A-Voce; 35", 1984
          Geosound-Geosonica; 4'25", 1984
          Con Sonanti; 4'35", 1984
          Miss-Mix; 2'50", 1984
          Labirinto; 8'40", 1984
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ac55aaf3-d298-4345-8fd2-d684b3bd588f
        - Geerken, Hartmut. Untitled, 1989 and 1990; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:32:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503769)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dcd6e103-e060-4f53-8f4c-65c614c7b266
        - Blank, J. Learning the Scales, 1985 January 1; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:10:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503777)
          A handwritten note on the audiocassette reads: To Henri with love.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f948cb8b-0a4d-47ef-8b47-fbd0703f5f13
        - Schenh'au[?], Valeri. Sense - non - sense, 1993; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:31:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503785)
          Pour Henri Chopin avec meilleutes salusations; Berlin, Studio Rudbert Music
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b3fcb08a-3b66-4c72-82dc-3958589f408d
        - B.V., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:28:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503793)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2b8c1eb8-b814-4ddd-8f9c-78fa21acca17
        - Rarabet, René, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:32:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503801)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8c5784e2-ab22-4abe-bd3e-7973f3bcce16
        - Schwerner and Stein. So Po Festival, 1980 April 13; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:19:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503819)
          A note included with the audiocassette reads: To England.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b9fa2321-4641-412d-b07e-f8cdb7125688
        - Charbonnier. Untitled, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:30:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503827)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2eb887d8-bce2-48ad-9318-23b01ebf1e75
        - Radio Bou[?] H. C., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:40:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503835)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&60436f90-3295-4552-8262-2bfa76a7c50d
        - Marlow, Jack. Song for Voices, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:24:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503843)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&59ded88b-a88f-4dd6-8cd2-abd5a540b3f7
        - Kraft, P. Marine, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:14:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503850)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fea855ec-07d1-4e74-a9c7-5a95ff268eab
        - Les Niches Heures de L'alphabet, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:25:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503868)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e4ae2834-3043-4473-842b-c909d1434172
        - V.M., Erik. To Henri, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:34:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503876)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fec63a13-0e82-4c90-bc52-6c31c409b6ec
        - Deuis chaus ou, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:25:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. A high amount of hiss and static can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503884)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&de300f0d-da6a-4285-b297-3edbe7aad99e
        - Higgins. Bodies Electric: Arches, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:22:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503892)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e20e9be7-0bd4-4e35-b514-45403fe339f2
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/Emissions 5 et 6, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:10:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503926)
          Emission 5, 37'
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1e7ab67f-75bb-408c-aa75-4ddbc070c474
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/ Emissions 7 et 8, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:17:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503900)
          Emission 7, 30'; Emission 8, 35'
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b610dbf5-4070-46d7-b2da-a635e3a6205c
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/Emissions 11 et 12, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:14:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503918)
          Emission 11, 35'
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b9334a52-0f29-472d-abb9-92c6a483a63b
        - Smith, Hazel and Dean, Roger. Serpent ex Spearhead, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:08:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503934)
          Contents on the audiocassette include: Signed Original and Simultaneity.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e65f0cf2-2e86-401f-91de-a7396fea8ee9
        - Manfredini, Federica. Half Drowning, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:35:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss and static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. Audio in the left channel is recorded at a very low level throughout the first 35 minutes of the program. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503942)
          A list of contents are included with the audiocassette.
          1. Half Drowning (3 movimenti), 6'
          2. Wasser War, 4'
          3. Dove Vado, 1' 40"
          4. Phoney, 6'
          5. My 5 Notes, 5'
          6. Frequenza, 7'
          7. See the Sea, 3' 30"
          8. Exchanges 2, 56"
          9. To Be or Not to Be, 1' 32"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2f8f803c-65d3-4de3-b375-c741518f1803
        - Chopin, Henri. A C R 2, 1987 March 22; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The program is recorded at a very high level. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503959)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ce30b934-7df4-4137-92b6-2d4db94279ae
        - Les Dossiers D'Espace 2: Poesie Sonore --1--, 1992 March 10; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503967)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9c055fc3-5754-448d-957e-641ad1ed3d49
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154277; (34 audiocassettes)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c591a004-5b67-4a6a-80f5-4507523141ab
        - Festival d'In(ter)ventions I: Neoson(g) Cabaret, 1985; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:56:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506317)
          Face A / Face B
          1. The Woeurks, 4:52
          2. Okarina, 3:41
          3. Même la Technologie Fragmente, 5:25
          4. News, 4:25
          5. Glass Lass, 2:54
          6. (Je n'ai goút à rien), 2:33
          7. Sphère Sonore, 5:09
          1. Kipchogue Keino, 5:39
          2. Bestiaire Urbain et Autres Civiltés Bizarres, 4:35
          3. Temps Réel, 1:04
          4. Quelques Formules Utiles, 6:34
          5. Sans Titre, 4:12
          6. Lecture Générale, 2:59
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09a397a5-ed81-4506-87c4-fa7512c3f4ab
        - Bang Crash Wallopp (Book 2), May 13; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:02:48 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506325)
          Live Saturday the 13th of May at the LMC.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fefe33fd-5aa3-48dd-9656-80b5dd0912e9
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore, 1972; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:19:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506333)
          The contents of this audiocassette are included.
          Side A
          1. Le Voyage Lablovelaire (August 1971), 11'42"
          2. Le Cri - Homage to Marcel Janco (September 1971), 7'08"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3d76aa00-c369-4e88-8dd3-cc860fa29305
        - Wendt, Larry. New and Slightly Used Text-Sound Compositions, 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:13:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506341)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6faa3697-df86-4344-bc01-e53b8eaf74b2
        - Wendt, Larry. Metropolitan Fractalizations, 1978 November 25; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:55:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506358)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b48ff567-07fa-4034-b86b-e31259dbda5d
        - Pisek, Bruno. Est Etiam in Dicendo Quidati Cantus Obscurior, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:14:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506366)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d04ef568-af84-4765-b338-ff316be5ed33
        - Éclaboussurés Et Realites, 1987; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:39:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506374)
          Les Cygnes
          Tessynabe
          Sentiers Battus
          Rain At One O'clock
          Lee Dernier Train
          In Die Production
          Strang I
          D. Generation
          Forch
          Strang IV
          Turbulence
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&54c3ec55-ad29-4bce-b92b-66e58812a475
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore Internationale, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:57:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio on the left channel is silent from 17:06-17:27. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506382)
          Seuphor, Michel. Tout en Roulant les RR
          Dufrêne, François. Les Joyeux Sisyphe II
          Heidsieck, Bernard. Démocratie
          Chopin, Henri. Le Parlement Européan
          de Vree, Paul. Magdalena, Appassionata, Lettervrouw
          Novak, Ladislav. Deux poèmes onomatopées
          Gysin, Brion. Junk is no good baby
          Mon, Franz. Ja-Nein-Parabel
          Rühm, Gerhard. Spricht 'über' Auditive Poesie
          Jandl, Ernst. Vom Lautgedicht
          Lora-Totino, Arrigo. 'Smoke Words' for H. Chopin
          Giorno, John. Raspberry
          Hanson, Sten. The Glorious Desertion
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ddeab58c-33f6-4edc-9abb-8e798e7ddd51
        - Dufrêne, François. Cantate des mots camés, 1971-1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:44:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506390)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&24999638-90cc-4267-91ed-14d35b253698
        - Micoski, Claude. Anthologie sonore de Poésie, 1989; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:29:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506408)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4fa928f3-3e0e-4f97-9c93-0bc37a5b0f76
        - Polipoesia Primera Antologia, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:04:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506416)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bc7e955d-6ba7-455d-9a99-cb867b59a438
        - Mann, Chris. doin 2s, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; There is deterioration to parts of this audiocassette (sticky shed syndrome). The tape has not been digitized. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506424)
        - Boeswillwald, P. Fous de Révolution, 1989; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:13:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506432)
          overture Danton
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5528e649-00ef-4dc1-9dcd-5d497d379938
        - In die Irre gent alles, 1992 November 19; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:34:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506440)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&10db52f7-f733-4c28-8268-5418187c0fcb
        - Sampler Cassette, 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506457)
          Side 1 / Side 2
          Rothenberg, Jerome. Singing his total translation of the 12th of the 17 "Horse Songs" in the blessingway of Frank Mitchell
          Excerpt from "March 1974" of Hannah Weiner's "Clairvoyant Journal"
          Schwerner, Armand. Translation of Sophocles' "Philoctetes"
          Holst, Spencer. "The Frog"
          Corner, Philip and Fontana, William. "Metal Meditations with Fontana"
          Mac Low, Jackson. Excerpt from "Homage to Leona Bleiweiss"
          Lockwood, Annea. "World Rhythms"
          Crow Dog, Leonard and Mary. Traditional Sioux Peyote Songs
          Schechner, Richard and McIntosh, Joan. A field recording of bamoo jew's harp music
          Morrow, Charlie. "Evening Star Chant"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1228f168-1fcd-4d80-ae7f-e15a9f4f7566
        - Seuphor, Michel. Quelque 60 du XXº siècle, 1990; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:42:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506465)
          Face 1 / Face 2
          Poème Modèle, 1926
          Poème 131, 1927
          Poème 132, 1927
          Sardaigne, 1926
          Poème 110, 1927
          Poème 111, 1927
          Tout en roulant les RR, 1927
          Sinnge sange, 1929
          Erreur Brevetée, 1929
          Cartes sur table, 1963
          Discours Politique, 1952
          Chant Toltèque, 1963
          Langue vivante, 1963
          Maille hillilil, 1962
          Chanson de la dernière chance, 1966
          Chanson porte-chance, 1966
          Pour la St Erasme, 1978
          Pour la St Oiseau, 1978
          Falamagre, 1963
          Chanson de la fatalité, 1966
          Pour la St Socrate, 1978
          Pour la St Spinoza, 1978
          Le nageur, 1960
          Comme le temps passe, 1962
          Les vieux amis, 1963
          Le Rossignol, 1964
          Fifèle à l'amour du jeu, 1973
          La Puste, 1972
          Investiture, 1973
          Un résumé de tout, 1973
          Communiqué, 1958
          Servir la Poésie, 1958
          Le nouveau-né, 1962
          Curriculum, 1972
          Lentement, 1960
          Prière sur l'Acropole, 1962
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e20b2fa3-3390-41c0-a911-1ebcff4c8fdb
        - Flynt, Henry. "You Are My Everlovin' " / "Celestial Power", 1980 and 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:28:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506473)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&881716c0-4de7-4216-a8fc-71cc3d35e0a2
        - Chinea, Mark. Hammersley, Richard. Radin, Nick. Tabor, Richard and Bekerian, Debra. The 4 Day Opportunity, 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506481)
          This is a performance from an arts festival at Reading University: 1979-06-28.
          view data
          alt sx
          Xpls x
          a contralaboration
          A Theory of Danoing
          a little sleepy
          some humus
          W - -
          Minimal Studies 2
          in working
          Room Studies Volume 1
          Cloud Chamber
          loam
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c3054eea-439b-466e-84e2-b6cedd70c2cf
        - Hudak, John. momentumless identity, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:01:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506499)
          "many sparrows"
          "the lost pleasures"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e0689e41-6476-46fe-85dd-b1ae182b400e
        - Owen Sound. Underwhich Audiographic Series, "Beyond the Range", 1980 September; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:18:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506507)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3555e34a-4ea1-4bcb-9bce-0671c048fb7f
        - Nitsch, Hermann. Orgelkonzert, 1986 December 9; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506515)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2d88bbd0-a086-46ad-bc80-2cf7e6a271aa
        - Paté de Voix, 1985; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:01:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506523)
          torino, giugno
          Side A / Side B
          1. Porta, P.
          2. Colonna, G.
          3. Sproccati, S.
          4. Arbizzani, L.
          5. Bertola, C.
          6. Xerra, W.
          7. Tramutoli, G.
          8. Collo, R.
          1. Totino, A. L.
          2. Trentini, R.
          3. Cena, S.
          4. Giachino, L.
          5. Olmeda, P.
          6. Henrard, A.
          7. Vitacchio, A.
          8. Gherini, A.
          9. Carollo, A.
          10. Servetti, M.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8cb6f0fc-c8db-4c0f-a80e-bec3061131ea
        - Wendt, Larry. World-Class Technology / Frog Hollow, San Jose, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:53:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506531)
          1. San Jose Holiday, 9' 36"
          2. Broken Crystals, 11' 41"
          3. A Word Processing, 6' 39"
          1. Painted Rocks, 11' 49"
          2. Reaqanomics, 4' 34"
          3. Zolmak the Zygon, 9' 5"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c853eadb-ef99-4c0d-97f9-56f6ce9ffdd8
        - Bertozzi. Fogli e acque, 1992; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:03:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Levels in audio varies throughout the first minute and a half of programming. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506549)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7ce3b400-ba3c-4ceb-b751-8d2eee30dd28
        - Prism International, 1990; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:56:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506556)
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "Shadows"
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "Naked with Thorns"
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "This Light Called Darkness"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Contributory Negligence"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Death in Bromley"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "A Bang and A Wimpy"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Libyan Students from Hell"
          Courtemanche, Peter. Excerpt from "Radio Journal"
          MacLeod, Scott. Excerpts from "The Drunken Jungle
          Skratz, G. P. and Davis, Bob. Excerpts from "Mass of the Scattered Almonds"
          McCaffery, Steve. "Anticollabora"
          McCaffery, Steve. "Childe Harold's Phonemage"
          Bakken, Dick. "Ya Hi Yu Niva
          Bakken, Dick. "How to Eat Corn"
          Bakken, Dick. "Om Raksha"
          Robertson, Wes. "Stopping by the Woods on a Snowy Evening" by Robert Frost
          Bissett, Bill. "liquid dansrs"
          Bissett, Bill. "caribu rd"
          Broomfield, Howard. Excerpt from "In Doig Peoples Ears"
          O'Callahan, Jay. "The Cliffs of Culdurragh"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a5bb7046-0333-4444-962c-59d028ae1b59
        - Seuphor, Michel., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:42:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506564)
          Sinnge sannge, 1929
          Discours Politique, 1962
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&986f6d8f-4128-483b-ae71-56cf6f7901d2
        - Lonsdale, Andy. "Ah ow Hurt!" / "Boxmusik", 1983; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:01:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506572)
          A special compilation for Henri Chopin. Dolby. Final performance in Sydney, 1983-07-23.
          "hostages"
          "dreaming"
          "the patient"
          "atomic disease"
          "prelude"
          "kommunion"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&42aa5d54-2ece-4db9-b2fb-4f113985d1b8
        - Marlow, Jack and Dana, Llys. Taliesin, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:56:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506580)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8ccc3db6-d86c-41eb-b558-61d141990fa6
        - Pavl, Al. Symptome 199.999, 1984-1990; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506598)
          de A à Z, 5'
          "Quelque Chose D'autre!", 16'
          "Motus Magnus", 4' 32"
          "abobo-esprit", 3' 54"
          "mille et un bonheurs obligatoires - voix Claire", 7'
          "mouvement", 6' 17"
          "nouveaux proverbes et petites comédies element terre, 8'